<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>PeakMaven</title>
    <link href="https://www.peakmaven.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.peakmaven.com" />
    <updated>2022-12-06T15:20:44+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Stefan Langwald</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.peakmaven.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Your partner in all things cyber security.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Langwald</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.peakmaven.com/peakmaven-is-a-cyber-security-consultancy/"/>
        <id>https://www.peakmaven.com/peakmaven-is-a-cyber-security-consultancy/</id>

        <updated>2022-12-06T15:20:44+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Advisory &amp; Implementation.&nbsp;We support you in the implementation of your IT security and stand by your side with know-how and experience. Training.&nbsp;Expand your technical and organizational know-how and create more security awareness among your employees. Compliance.&nbsp;Is your business is considered critical infrastructure? Do you need&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p class="align-center">
    <span style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: 1em; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"></span>
  </p>

    <h2 id="services">
      Services
    </h2>

  <p>
    <strong>Advisory &amp; Implementation.&nbsp;</strong>We support you in the implementation of your IT security and stand by your side with know-how and experience.
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>Training.</b>&nbsp;Expand your technical and organizational know-how and create more security awareness among your employees. 
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>Compliance.</b>&nbsp;Is your business is considered critical infrastructure? Do you need to comply with any regulatory framework before the next funding round? We help you to achieve any objective.
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>Certification.&nbsp;</b>Build trust and verify information security with official certification. We accompany you through the audit. No matter if ISO 27001, SOC/2, or PCI-DSS.&nbsp;
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>Audit.&nbsp;</b>We carry out internal audits for you, at your premises or at your suppliers. And we provide potential for improvement with concrete recommendations.
  </p>

  <p>
    <b>GDPR.</b>&nbsp;We help your business in all matters for GDPR compliance.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
